- Greetings, Seller University.
My name is Matt Jones.
I'm the co-founder of Crease Beast,
the world's most comfortable crease protector
for sneaker heads.
We've been utilizing Amazon over the past five years
to grow our small niche product
into a global conglomerate.
Today, I'm gonna share a few tools
that we've used along the way
that will help grow your brand as well.
First is Amazon FBA.
As opposed to fulfilling your orders by yourselves,
you can send your products directly to  Amazon
and they'll fulfill your orders for you.
Not only do they handle customer service and returns,
it also gives your products the Amazon Prime tag,
which makes them way more attractive to buyers
and they sell a lot faster.
You should also check out Amazon Vine.
It's a way to get your products ranked higher
by giving out free samples in exchange for reviews.
If you have any protections on your brand,
like trademarks, you can upload them
to Amazon's brand registry to prevent any sellers
from copying your likeness.
If you get your products manufactured in other countries,
you can utilize Amazon's global logistics,
which helps your supply chain run a lot more efficiently.
You can get your products sent directly
from your manufacturer straight to FBA.
You can also check out the other marketplaces on Amazon.
You can utilize their fulfillment centers
in other countries like the UK, Germany,
and Spain like we do for our brand
and that'll help grow your brand a lot faster
if you can send your products from your manufacturers
to other countries to fulfill.
You will need VATs in these other countries
to have your products be sold from their fulfillment centers,
but it's worth it if your brand has worldwide appeal
and it'll grow your brand a lot faster.
These are a few tools that we've used over the years
that have helped grow our brand
and help you check them out as well.